# **Calvin Seok**

(213) 434-1131 | calvinseok@gmail.com | Torrance, CA |

#### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Dedicated IT leader with comprehensive knowledge in hardware and software maintenance, information security experience, and in-depth understanding of cloud-based solutions. Proactive in implementing updates and solutions with minimal downtime and adept at troubleshooting technical issues resulting in quick resolutions. Fluent in Korean.

# INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY COMPETENCIES

**Systems:** Windows PC, Mac OS and iOS, Linux

Cloud Service: AWS

Languages: SQL, Python

**Software:** MS Word/Excel/PowerPoint/Outlook

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

• AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

• AWS Certified Developer - Associate

AWS Certified SysOps Administrator - Associate

CompTIA A+

CompTIA Security+

CompTIA Network+

CompTIA Cloud+

CompTIA Project+

LPI Linux Essentials

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Support Desk Specialist III - Spectrum Networks | El Segundo, CA

May 2023 – present

Ensure the stable operation of computer hardware, software systems and network/server infrastructure. Install, deploy, support and maintain computer hardware and imaging. Monitor cybersecurity metrics and patch local machines.

- Provision/deprovision AWS EC2 VMs and monitor S3 bucket usage.
- Evaluate and analyze systems and metrics in order to provide recommendations for service improvements.
- Perform in-depth analysis and detailed reporting on operating system and major application software patch assessment and security vulnerability analysis.
- Review and update service policies and procedures to safeguard critical systems, information and data.
- Create and maintain high-quality documentation of all relevant specifications, systems, and procedures.

## Help Desk Support Specialist – Sun Auto Tire & Service | Torrance, CA

March 2022 – May 2023

Remotely provided Tier 1 IT support through VOIP and email. Troubleshoot hardware, software, and network issues.

- Performed duties as a member of the IT support team for a national tire and service company.
- Diagnose and remediate systems and software
- Deployed patches and updates to ensure security compliance.
- Researched, responded to and resolved escalated issues/problems

## Help Desk Support - El Camino College | Torrance, CA

August 2020 - March 2022

Help Desk worker for the IT department at a community college. Responsible for maintaining inventory of laptops for students.

- Performed duties for the IT support team at a community college while still a student.
- Prepared and distributed loaner laptops for students
- Update and maintain spreadsheet databases of inventory.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science in Cloud Computing**

May 2024

Western Governors University | Salt Lake City, UT

- Studies focused in cloud platforms, software, and practical application of cloud computing infrastructure
- Courses included IT systems and services, networking and security, scripting and programming, data management, and cloud platforms.